aboutcivil.org 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy Notice

**WebTechTix** know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting **aboutcivil.org** , you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

## What Personal Information About Customers Does aboutcivil.org Gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at **aboutcivil.org**. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, customizing future visits for you, improving our web features, and communication with you.

  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our website.
  * Moreover, we have placed **Google Adsense** for the purpose of helping ourselves bear the charges of our website e.g Hosting. **Google** takes into record your visits and use them for displaying ads very based on Page Content and very similar to your area of interests. No. of visits and the websites you visit tell google about your area of interest. We are in no way related to **Google Inc** and the way **Google** uses your data is purely for your benefit. Neither **aboutcivil.org** or **Google** exchange any information about our visitors directly or in any other way. 

  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more productive to improve service and your shopping experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products, notifications of changes to our policies, and order confirmations. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, other than order notifications and receipts, please adjust your "Subscription" preferences by logging into your account.

## What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as downloads, Pages Viewed, Visits, Keywords etc. 

## Does aboutcivil.org Share the Information It Receives?

We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your request or to help you out.   

## Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit **aboutcivil.org** , your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of our local state. If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough description by clicking on the "Contact Us" link on the side menu, and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

## Automatic Information

For security purposes **aboutcivil.org** sometimes collects and analyzes the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, and to our website. This is done for our protection to keep ourselves safe from Bandwidth problems and any other malicious activity in the site.   

## Questions

Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us" link in the side menu. Or you can email us at: [haseebjamal_stn@yahoo.com](mailto:haseebjamal_stn@yahoo.com)

## Civil Engineering Dictionary Android App

We personally collect no information from the user whatsoever. But, we have placed **Google Adsense** for the purpose of helping ourselves bear the charges of developing further this application. **Google** takes into record your visits and use them for displaying ads based on your search history, apps installed and very similar to your area of interests. We are in no way related to **Google Inc** and the way **Google** uses your data is purely for your benefit. Neither **aboutcivil.org** or **Google** exchange any information about our visitors directly or in any other way. 

Thank you for your Understanding and Support.
